igyaan.in 2019-04-26

# Privacy & Disclaimer | iGyaan Network

Below is information regarding iGyaan Networks, which includes http://www.iGyaan.in Networks, http://Trendpolice.com, http://EatBurpRepeat.com and http://www.AutoGyaan.com, commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet.

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to iGyaan Network . The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. If for any reason you have concerns about our software or website’s privacy policies, please contact us. We are committed to ensuring that every user’s needs are addressed.

### Collection of Personal Information

In the course of delivering this site to you, iGyaan Networks does NOT collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address from users of this web site without your knowledge, and are taking measures to protect your privacy.

You can send email requesting help and your email will NOT be shared in any way with any third party(ies), and will only be used to send replies to you.

Ads used on this website can use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process. You can remove them at any time using your browser tools.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this matter, please feel free to [contact us.](https://www.igyaan.in/contact-us/ "Contact Us")

### Ads on iGyaan Network:

We may also share certain information such as your location, browser, and cookie data and other data relating to your use of our Service with our business partners to deliver advertisements (“ads”) that may be of interest to you. iGyaan Network may allow third-party ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements on the Service. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser or mobile device, the ads and ad links that appear on the Service, and will automatically receive your IP address when they do so. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, device identifiers, location data, and clear gifs, see above) to compile information about your browser’s or device’s visits and usage patterns on the Service and on other websites, and to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize the advertising content delivered to you.

For example, Google uses DART cookies in order to deliver ads to you through the Service. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to the Service and previous websites that you may have visited. Other advertising networks also use similar cookies, clear gifs, or other mechanisms to deliver targeted advertising to you through the Service.  You may opt out of use of Google’s DART cookie and cookies placed by Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) certified ad networks here:<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> . Opting out of these cookies will be effective not only on the Service, but on all websites with NAI certified advertising networks. However, these opt-outs will be ineffective on networks that are not NAI certified.

Please note that an advertiser may ask iGyaan to show an ad to a certain audience of Users (e.g., based on demographics or other interests). In that situation, iGyaan or our Partners determines the target audience and iGyaan serves the advertising to that audience and only provides anonymous data to the advertiser. If you respond to such an ad, the advertiser or ad server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.

To enhance your user experience or help us improve and measure our effectiveness, iGyaan Network may embed code from third parties on the Service. Examples of such parties may include Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Google, YouTube, Howcast, VideoJug, AOL, and others. These third parties may collect information about you including IP address, cookies in ways iGyaan does not control.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

The iGyaan Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of third-parties. Please consult the respective privacy policies of such third parties or contact such third parties for more information.

### Burst Direct:

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Disclaimer:

The contents of this report are based on information generally available to the public from sources believed to be reliable. No representation is made that it is timely, accurate or complete. iGyaan has taken due care and caution in compilation of data as this has been obtained from various sources including which it considers reliable and first hand. However, iGyaan does not guarantee the accuracy, adequacy or completeness of any information and it is not responsible for any errors or omissions or for the results obtained from the use of such information and especially states that it has no financial liability whatsoever to the subscribers / users of this report. The information herein, together with all estimates and forecasts, can change without notice.

This report does not purport to be a solicitation of any advice pertaining to trade and business and readers are advised to consult experts or study / evaluate individual business prospectus and other relevant legal documents before taking any decisions based on information provided in the site. Neither iGyaan nor its Directors or Analysts or Employees accept any liability whatsoever nor do they accept responsibility for any financial consequences arising from the use of the research or information provided herein.

### Links to Other Websites and Services

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from the Service, including the information or content contained therein. Please remember that when you use a link to go from the Service to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or service, including those that have a link or advertisement on our website, are subject to that third party’s own rules and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and we do not control over any third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or service (like Facebook, Google groups, or an IRC chatroom) and you allow such a third-party access to you User Content you do so at your own risk. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources other than through the Service.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

iGyaan may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect the changes in our business and practices, and so you should review this page periodically. When we change the policy in a material manner we will let you know and update the ‘last modified’ date at the bottom of this page.

This privacy policy was last modified on June 7th 2014

#### iGyaan Networks Privacy and Disclaimer Team
